<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">

<g:HTMLPanel styleName="acknowledgements">
<h1>Kuali Student Acknowledgements</h1>
<p><g:Label ui:field='verLabel'/></p>
<p>Copyright 2010 The Kuali Foundation. All rights reserved. Kuali is licensed for use pursuant to the Educational Community License v. 2.0. Portions of Kuali are copyrighted by other parties, including the parties listed below. You should refer to the licenses directory for complete copyright and licensing information. Questions about licensing should be directed to <a href="mailto:license@kuali.org">license@kuali.org</a>.</p>
<p>The Kuali Foundation Educational Community License 2.0: Kuali Rice API, Kuali Rice Implementation, Kuali Rice Web</p>

<h2>Third Party Contributions</h2>
<p>Portions of Kuali were developed by The University of British Columbia, University of Maryland College Park, University of California Berkeley, Florida State University, San Joaquin Delta Community College, The University of Washington, University of Southern California, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Carnegie Mellon University and Naval Post Graduate School. (<a href="http://www.kuali.org/" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://www.kuali.org/</a>).</p>

<p>This product includes software developed by ANTLR (<a href="http://www.antlr.org/" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://www.antlr.org/</a>).</p>

<p>This product includes software developed by the Apache Software Foundation (<a href="http://www.apache.org" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://www.apache.org</a>).</p>

<p>This product includes software developed by CDDL (<a href="http://www.opensource.org/" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://www.opensource.org/</a>).</p>

<p>This product includes software developed by Junit  (<a href="http://www.junit.org/" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://www.junit.org/</a>).</p>

<p>This product includes software developed by ECLIPSE (<a href="http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.htm" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.htm</a>).</p>

<p>This product includes software licensed under GNU Lesser General Public License (<a href="http://www.opensource.org/licenses/lgpl-license.php" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://www.opensource.org/licenses/lgpl-license.php</a>).</p>

<p>This product includes software developed by HOWL (<a href="http://hsqldb.org" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://hsqldb.org</a>).</p>

<p>This product includes software developed by JDOM (<a href="http://www.jdom.org/" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://www.jdom.org/</a>).</p>

<p>This product includes software developed by the Open Symphony Group (<a href="http://www.opensymphony.com/" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://www.opensymphony.com/</a>).</p>

<p>This product includes the Kuali Rice module licensed under the Kuali Foundation ECL (Rice Acknowledgments).</p>

<p>This product includes software developed by Xstream (<a href="http://xstream.codehaus.org/" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://xstream.codehaus.org/</a>).</p>

<p>Portions Copyright (c) 2000-2006 The Legion of the Bouncy Castle. All Rights Reserved. (<a href="http://www.bouncycastle.org" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://www.bouncycastle.org</a>).</p>

<p>Portions Copyright (c) 2001-2006 Sun Microsystems, Inc. All Rights Reserved.</p>

<p>Portions Copyright (c) 2007, JA-SIG, Inc. All Rights Reserved.</p>

<p>Portions Copyright (c) 2000-2005 INRIA, France Telecom. All Rights Reserved.</p>

<p>Portions Copyright (c) 2003-2005 Joe Walnes. All Rights Reserved. (<a href="http://xstream.codehaus.org/" class="external-link" rel="nofollow">http://xstream.codehaus.org/</a>).</p>
  	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 