<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">

	
  <ui:style>
  .helpTable{
  	margin-left: 20px;
  	margin-right: 20px;
  	margin-bottom: 10px;
  }
  
  .helpTable td{
  	padding-top: 3px;
  	padding-bottom: 3px;
  }
  
  .tableSectionHeader td{
  		font-weight: bold;
  		background-color: gainsboro;
  		border-right: 1px solid white;
  		padding-right: 10px;
  }

  </ui:style>

  <g:HTMLPanel>
  	<table class='{style.helpTable}'>
  		<tr class='{style.tableSectionHeader}'>
  			<td width='30%'>Courses and course proposals</td>
  			<td></td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>View a course or browse the catalog?</td>
  			<td>Under View and Modify, use the search box to find a specific course. To browse
the catalog, click on the Browse the catalog link, located under the search box.</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>Propose a new course?</td>
  			<td>Under Create, use the dropdown to select the type of course you want to propose.
This will start a new course proposal.</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>Modify a course</td>
  			<td>Under View and Modify, use the search box to locate the course you want to
modify. Then use the dropdown 'Proposal Actions', just below the course title,
and select 'Modify this Course' which will start a modification proposal.</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>Modify a group of courses at once?</td>
  			<td>Under View and Modify, click on the manage a group link. The system will ask
you to identify the courses you wish to modify, and you will start a modification
proposal.</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>Check the status of my course proposal?</td>
  			<td>Under Create, click the See my proposed courses link. This will take you to the
outbox section of your Action List, where you will see a list of documents. Find
the document you wish to check, and open it to reveal the document log.</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>See what proposals are in review?</td>
  			<td>Under View and Modify, you can search for proposals using the search box.
Just change the dropdown from Courses to Proposals.</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>Approve (or reject) a course proposal?</td>
  			<td>Under the Navigate to dropdown, select My Actionlist. This will take you to
your list of Kuali Student documents and processes requiring your attention. You
can sort the list by document type, and then proceed through the list of course
proposals. In order to approve or reject a proposal, select it from the list. It will
open on the summary page, where you can review the proposal. Use the
Workflow Actions dropdown to make a decision for the proposal.</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr class='{style.tableSectionHeader}'>
  			<td>Programs</td>
  			<td></td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>View program details? (entrance or
completion requirements)</td>
  			<td>Under View and Modify, use the search box to find a specific program. To
browse the catalog, click on the Browse the catalog link, located under the
search box.</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>Edit a program?</td>
  			<td>Under View and Modify, use the search box to locate the program you want to
modify. Then use the Edit link, in the left navigation panel, which will take you into
an editable mode for the program.</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr class='{style.tableSectionHeader}'>
  			<td>Other Curriculum Tools</td>
  			<td></td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>View a course set or build a new one?</td>
  			<td>Under Curriculum Tools, click on the Course Sets link, where you will have the
option to search for a course set or create a new one.</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>Manage course and program fees for my
department?</td>
  			<td>Under Curriculum Tools, click on the Fees link, where you will have the option to
search for a fee or create a new one.</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>Manage Learning Objectives?</td>
  			<td>Under Curriculum Tools, click on the Learning Objectives link, where you will
have the option to search for a Learning Objective or create a new one.</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td>Run analysis (examine prerequisite chains)</td>
  			<td>Under Curriculum Tools, click on the Run Analysis link, where you can enter the
course you wish to run analysis on.</td>
  		</tr>
  	</table>
  </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 