<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">

	
  <ui:style>
  .helpTable{
  	margin-left: 20px;
  	margin-right: 20px;
  	margin-bottom: 10px;
  }
  
  .helpTable td{
  	padding-top: 3px;
  	padding-bottom: 3px;
  }
  
  .tableSectionHeader td{
  		font-weight: bold;
  		background-color: gainsboro;
  		border-right: 1px solid white;
  		padding-right: 10px;
  }

  </ui:style>

  <g:HTMLPanel>
<table class='{style.helpTable}'>
    <tr class='{style.tableSectionHeader}'>
     <td width='30%'>Courses and Course Proposals</td>
     <td></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>View a course or browse the catalog?</td>
     <td>Under <b>Find Courses and Programs</b>, select a link to locate a course or program. To browse the catalog, click <a href="#/HOME/CURRICULUM_HOME/COURSE_CATALOG">Browse Course Catalog</a>.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>Propose a new course?</td>
     <td>Under <b>Proposals</b>, select <a href="#/HOME/CURRICULUM_HOME/COURSE_PROPOSAL">Propose a Course</a>. This will start a new course proposal.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>Modify a course?</td>
     <td>Under <b>Find Courses and Programs</b>, click <b>Find Courses</b> locate the course you want to modify. Then use the dropdown <b>'Proposal Actions'</b>, just below the course title, and select <b>'Modify this Course'</b>. This will start a modification proposal. </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>Check the status of my course proposal?</td>
     <td>Under <b>Proposals</b>, click <a href="#/HOME">My Actionlist</a>. Then go to the outbox section of your Action List, where you will see a list of documents. Find the document you wish to check, and open it to review the document log. </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>See what proposals are in review?</td>
     <td>Under <b>Proposals</b>, you can search for proposals using the <b>Find Course Proposals</b> link</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>Approve (or reject) a course proposal?</td>
     <td>Under <b>Proposals</b>, click <a href="#/HOME">My Actionlist</a>.   This will take you to your list of Kuali Student documents and processes requiring your attention. You can sort the list by document type, and then proceed through the list of course proposals.  In order to approve or reject a proposal, select it from the list. It will open on the summary page, where you can review the proposal. Use the Workflow Actions dropdown to make a decision for the proposal. </td>
    </tr>
    <tr class='{style.tableSectionHeader}'>
     <td>Programs</td>
     <td></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>View program details? (entrance or completion requirements)</td>
     <td>Under <b>Find Courses and Programs</b>, click the Find Programs link to locate the  program. To browse the catalog, click <a href="#/HOME/CURRICULUM_HOME/COURSE_CATALOG">Browse Course Catalog</a>.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>Edit a program?</td>
     <td>Under <b>Find Courses and Programs</b>, click <b>Find Programs</b> to locate the program. Then click the <b>Edit</b> link in the left navigation panel, which will activate an editable mode for the program. </td>
    </tr>
    <tr class='{style.tableSectionHeader}'>
     <td>Other Curriculum Tools</td>
     <td></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>View a course set or build a new one?</td>
     <td>Under <b>Management Tools</b>, click <a href="#/HOME/CURRICULUM_HOME/CLU_SETS">Course Set Management</a>, where you will have the option to search for a course set or create a new one</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>Manage Learning Objectives? (coming soon)</td>
     <td>Under Management Tools, click on the Learning Objectives, where you will have the option to search for a Learning Objective or create a new one.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>Run analysis (examine prerequisite chains)? (coming soon)</td>
     <td>Under Management Tools, click on the Run Analysis link, where you can enter the course you want to run analysis on.</td>
    </tr>
   </table>
  </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 